<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Services on N3tLabs</title><link>/services/</link><description>Recent content in Services on N3tLabs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 16:56:46 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Custom Data Solutions</title><link>/services/custom/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate><guid>/services/custom/</guid><description>Is there a specific type of data that you need access on the blockchain that is not yet available?
We&amp;rsquo;re able to help you connect your existing API to smart contract applications. Talk with our team and we can help you create an external adapter to easily and security get you desired data set into the desired blockchain of your choice.</description></item><item><title>External Adapters</title><link>/services/external_adapters/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 16:56:46 +1000</pubDate><guid>/services/external_adapters/</guid><description>Is there an existing external adapter you would like for us to implement?
What is an external adapter? External adapters allow additional flexibility to Chainlink Oracles such as querying API&amp;rsquo;s that require authentication or performing additional operations on data before returning it on-chain. For more information on external adapters view the Chainlink documentation
We have experience in creating custom external adapters.</description></item><item><title>Node as a Service</title><link>/services/node_as_service/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 16:56:46 +1000</pubDate><guid>/services/node_as_service/</guid><description>Interested in easily deploying and running you own Chainlink node without needing developer experience?
We can deploy managed nodes to the network of your choice. We manage the infrastructure, you manage the node configuration from the easily to use UI. For more information on managed nodes contact us</description></item></channel></rss>